{"location": "Brock Sport Facilities", "town": "St. Catharines", "description": "Brock University features a number of state-of-the-art athletic facilities. The Eleanor Misener Aquatic Centre, the largest swimming facility in Niagara, is named after the late Eleanor Misener, a local advocate for accessible exercise facilities and founder of the St. Catharines chapter of the Multiple Sclerosis Society. The 50-metre Olympic-size pool has hosted numerous meets. The complex also features one artificial turf field, Alumni Field, and two grass fields. These fields will host the women\u2019s rugby sevens, which will mark the first time this event has been featured at a Canada Games.", "events": ["Rugby Sevens", "Diving", "Swimming"]}
{"location": "Brock University", "town": "St. Catharines", "description": "Brock University will be home to the Cycling Criterium. The course will run around the roundabout central to Brock\u2019s St. Catharines campus. A short loop with curved corners, this course will provide a fast paced race in the heart of the Athletes Village.", "events": ["Cycling"]}
{"location": "Canada Games Park", "town": "Thorold", "description": "A legacy project for Niagara 2022 Canada Summer Games, Canada Games Park is located at Brock University, south of the main campus. The facility includes the Walker Sports and Abilities Centre consisting of two ice pads, a para sport gymnasium with four courts, a health and wellbeing centre and a 200m indoor track. Outside, there will be six beach volleyball courts, a cycling centre, an outdoor storage area, and a track-and-field facility including a full 400m track and areas for all disciplines (jumps and throws).", "events": ["Athletics", "Beach Volleyball", "Box Lacrosse", "Wrestling", "Volleyball"]}
{"location": "Etobicoke Olympium", "town": "Etobicoke", "description": "Located on the edge of Centennial Park and home to many sports clubs including the Etobicoke Diving Club, the Etobicoke Olympium is a premiere multi-sport facility that has hosted countless national and international events. The facility underwent major renovations as a result of the Toronto 2015 Pan American Games, where it was used as the primary aquatics training venue. The eight-lane, 50-metre competition pool will host Niagara 2022\u2019s 3-metre and platform (10-metre) diving competitions.", "events": ["Diving"]}
{"location": "Legends on the Niagara Golf Course - Battlefield Course", "town": "Niagara Falls", "description": "The Legends on the Niagara Battlefield Course is located on the grounds of the Battle of Chippewa, which took place on July 5, 1814 during the War of 1812. The Legends on the Niagara Golf Course opened in 2002 and is home to two championship courses and a par-3 executive course for a total of 45 holes.", "events": ["Golf"]}
{"location": "Meridian Centre", "town": "St. Catharines", "description": "The Meridian Centre is the Niagara region\u2019s largest entertainment facility and has hosted many significant events. In the spring and summer months, Meridian is the home of the Niagara River Lions of the Canadian Elite Basketball League, and in the winter, the Niagara IceDogs of the Ontario Hockey League. The Meridian Centre will kick off the Niagara 2022 Canada Summer Games with the Opening Ceremony.", "events": ["Basketball"]}
{"location": "Niagara College Welland Campus", "town": "Welland", "description": "Niagara College has a history of athletic excellence. The Niagara College Knights host five varsity sports teams (mens and womens) as well as numerous intramural sports teams. Updated in 2011 through a $90 million campus redevelopment project, the Niagara College athletic facilities are top tier.", "events": ["Basketball", "Volleyball"]}
{"location": "Niagara-on-the-Lake Sailing Club", "town": "Niagara-on-the-Lake", "description": "Nestled on the shores of the Niagara River, the Niagara-on-the-Lake Sailing Club is one of Lake Ontario\u2019s premier sailing destinations. The Club is home to an active junior sailing program, club and class racing fleets and welcomes cruisers from all over the lake to the Niagara region. The Club shares hosting of the Niagara 2022 Canada Summer Games with the Dalhousie Yacht Club.", "events": ["Sailing"]}
{"location": "Niagara-on-the-Lake Tennis Club", "town": "Niagara-on-the-Lake", "description": "The Niagara-on-the-Lake Tennis Club located at Memorial Park has been providing an opportunity for members to play tennis since 1970. An active club that has been playing on four hard courts, they will be expanding their facility with the addition of two more courts in the spring of 2021.", "events": ["Tennis"]}
{"location": "Oakes Park", "town": "Niagara Falls", "description": "Oakes Park is one of Niagara Falls' busiest public facilities. The baseball diamond is part of a facility that opened on the Civic Holiday in 1931 and features a soccer field, track, playground and an additional baseball diamond.", "events": ["Baseball"]}
{"location": "Port Colborne", "town": "Port Colborne", "description": "Located on Lake Erie, Port Colborne is the southern port of entry of the Welland Canal. Following the completion of the canal in 1833, this small settlement on Gravelly Bay was named a port-of-entry in 1834 and given its present name in honour of Upper Canada's then Lieutenant-Governor Sir John Colborne, who was instrumental in securing funding for the canal project. The Time Trial will take place around H.H. Knoll Lakeview Park.", "events": ["Cycling"]}
{"location": "Royal Canadian Henley Rowing Course", "town": "St. Catharines", "description": "A world class rowing facility, the Royal Canadian Henley Rowing Course hosted the World Rowing Championships in 1999 and will host them for the third time in 2024. Located in historic Port Dalhousie, St. Catharines, the course dates back to 1903 and has been hosting events ever since including the Royal Canadian Henley Regatta and the Toronto 2015 Pan American Games.", "events": ["Rowing"]}
{"location": "Southward Park", "town": "Grimsby", "description": "Southward Community Sports Park located in Grimsby recently opened in May of 2017. The park features baseball/softball diamonds, soccer fields, 2.5km of walking trails, a dog park, playground, and bocce ball courts.", "events": ["Softball"]}
{"location": "Town of Pelham", "town": "Fonthill", "description": "The Town of Pelham includes the communities of Fonthill, Fenwick, North Pelham and Ridgeville. Pelham is primarily an agricultural area where many farms abound. The Cycling Road Race that winds through local orchards and vineyards will start and finish at Town Square in downtown Fonthill.", "events": ["Cycling"]}
{"location": "Twelve Mile Creek", "town": "St. Catharines", "description": "Nestled along the newly built and picturesque trails of Twelve Mile Creek, the 4km course for Mountain Bike will begin with a steep climb up Hydro Hill and will continue to loop around the escarpment with new legacy features such as a rock garden and gap jumps to challenge athletes.", "events": ["Mountain Bike"]}
{"location": "Welland Baseball Stadium", "town": "Welland", "description": "Located in the centre of the Niagara Region in Welland, the Welland Baseball Stadium was originally built for the Pittsburgh Pirates minor league team that played at the stadium from 1989 to 1995. The Stadium has seen action from a number of leagues and is home to the Welland Jackfish of the Intercounty Baseball League.", "events": ["Baseball"]}
{"location": "Welland International Flatwater Centre", "town": "Welland", "description": "The Welland International Flatwater Centre is located at the south end of the Welland Recreational Waterway. The Waterway used to be a part of the canal connecting Lake Ontario to Lake Erie and was closed to ships with the creation of the Welland Bypass in the 1970s. A legacy of the TORONTO 2015 Pan American Games, the Welland International Flatwater Centre consists of a timing tower, a training centre, seating for 500 and multi-functional modular docking.", "events": ["Canoe Kayak", "Triathlon", "Swimming"]}
{"location": "Welland Tennis Club", "town": "Welland", "description": "The Welland Tennis Club was formed in 1913 on the site of am old brickyard, hence the red clay courts. In the late 1970s, four additional hard courts with lighting were added to the club and have been actively used ever since. The club also is home to a vibrant junior program and continues to be the source of provincial and national level competitors.", "events": ["Tennis"]}
{"location": "Youngs Sportsplex", "town": "Welland", "description": "Youngs Sportsplex opened in 2012 and quickly elevated the sports scene across the Niagara Region. The multi-sport complex features a FIFA regulation size indoor soccer field, four indoor tennis courts and a number of additional recreation areas. Surrounding the complex are five regulation soccer fields, three of which are artificial turf fields. The facility hosts numerous sports and provides a venue for recreational/competitive athletes to train all year round.", "events": ["Soccer"]}